

ABOUT ME

I am a beginner programmer with a deep interest in the Webdevelopment. I have been studying programming for 1.5 years. I have basic knowledge in languages PHP(OOP), MySQL as well as experience in developing web applications on Laravel framework using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap. Wrote several Petprojects, with examples you can look at GitHub. Completed courses on the basics of algorithms and data structures and design patterns. Actively adhere to the standards for writting PSR code. I am sure that my motivation and desire to learn new will allow me to successfully achieve my professional goals and achieve success in a career as a programmer

LINKS

Portfolio:

https://pshenychnyi-portfolio.vercel.app/

GitHub:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/pshen
ychnyi_artem/

Telegram:@APshenychnyi

Viber: +421951218226

ARTEM PSHENYCHNYI

FULL - STACK DEVELOPER

Na pažiti, Trenčín, 911 01, Slovakia

+421951218226

artem0096@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

AI STARTUP

Trenčin Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

LARAVEL DEVELOPER

My first commercial experience was a website generator. This startup is aimed at the US and Canadian markets. The project was written with the Laravel framework and using AI to generate pages.

ARTEM PSHENYCHNYI

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

WFB DEVELOPMENT

Mini CRM system. Written in the Vue framework 3. In this project, I used such tools like Vue-cli, Vue-router, Vuex as well Materialize elements. authentication system and registration implemented using the database Firebase

Git repository:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/mini_crm_system

ARTEM PSHENYCHNYI

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

WEB DEVELOPMENT

The second project is an online fruit store.

Written in the Laravel framework using MySQL databases. The site consists of user part and administrative panels. For custom form processing parts and adding / removing goods to / from the basket asynchronous requests are used. On the site there is a full-fledged basket, and there is also comment block.

Git repository:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/fruitshop.loc

ARTEM PSHENYCHNYI Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

WEB DEVELOPMENT

My first Pet-project - Corporate site. Wrien in the Laravel framework. It has administrative and user part with using a MySQL database. JavaScript elements used to highlight the active item menu, send an asynchronous request to the server, and form processing.

Git repository:

https://github.com/Pshnychnyi/it.loc

EDUCATION

ZATK

Zhytomyr 2016

NUBIP

Kiev 2020 Some College (no degree)

Bachelor

SKILLS

PHP ENGLISH (PRE-INTEMIDIATE)

LARAVEL MYSQL

JAVASCRIPT VUEJS

GIT HTML/CSS